MARTIN CHRISTENSEN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mc1995/

martinchristensen.netlify.app/

SUMMARY

I have approximately two years of experience as a Full-stack developer with a B.Eng in Robot Systems from the University of Southern Denmark, in Europe's robot capital, Odense. I am detail-oriented, analytical, and always on the lookout for ways to improve efficiency. I have a deep interest in technology and I am eager to learn new things. As a Full-stack developer, I have been responsible for implementing responsive web pages with the necessary back and front end functionalities for the best possible user experience. Throughout my work and studies, I have shown my capability to work independently and in teams.

EDUCATION

B.Eng. Robot systems

2018 - 2022

University of Southern Denmark, Faculty of Engineering

I gained the qualifications to be able to lead the development of robot technology products, solve complex technical development tasks, collaborate on professional and interdisciplinary projects, develop mobile phones, web applications, security systems and much more.

Diploma Web-integrator

2013 - 2015

Viden Djurs

I gained theoretical knowledge and practical skills to produce web solutions on different platforms, such as websites and apps for tablets and phones. Experience in web development including functionality and design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer

Aug. 2020 - present

Frydendal-IT

- Development of web-based CRM system for a facility service client
- Seeing tasks through from idea brainstorming to complete implementation
- Thoroughly testing of the platforms functionalities for all user types
- Analyze project progress, adapt scope and timelines to ensure the project requirements are met
- Collaborate with team to ensure applications align with the customer needs
- Actively participate in weekly project meetings
- Server side exporting data from website tables and database to xlsx and csv files
- CSS styling with bootstrap
- IDE: PhpStorm
- Php web framework: Laravel

Mentor Aug. 2018 - Jan. 2019

MentorDanmark

- Assisted Gymnasium (≈High School) students with math homework
- Delivered concepts and proofs in mathematics in a comprehensive way.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Chairman 2016

Denmark's Social Democratic Youth Skanderborg

- Planned meetings, campaigns, and other events.
- Contributed in meetings with the leadership of the local department of the Social Democratic

Vice-Chairman 2017

VUC Aarhus

- Represented more than 2000 adult students as vice- chairman in VUC Aahus student union
- Planned student activities and contributed in budget meetings with the school's leadership.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, C, C++, C#, Javascript, React, HTML, CSS, Php, Laravel, Json, Adobe Photoshop, InDesign and Illustrator, Microsoft Office, MATLAB